

Antonio <u>Garcia</u>

Full Stack Developer

Maril.com ≥ black.cat01312@gmail.com

+63(2)8907620

• Makati City, Philippines

03/12/1994

Male

Serbia

S live:.cid.1e2d8062cd1d3619

https://github.com/white01312

■ ② ② Sunshinee 0213

Profile

THIS IS HOW I SEE MYSELF

Passionate and experienced Senior Web Developer with 7 years of web industry experience

Advanced knowledge of multiple programming languages and extensive familiarity with several database structure

Specialize MERN Stack development

Strong analytical, problem-solving and trouble shooting skills

Constantly delivering web development projects under budget and within deadline

Constantly learning new programs, languages, and best practices in full stack development

Positive Attitude, good team player

Wholly focused on client satisfaction and event success

Languages

English



Education

Western Mindanao State University

2010 - 2015

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Zamboanga City, Philippines

Completed of duties as a teaching and research assistant for the computer science department

Skills			
HTML	• • • •	Python	• • • • •
CSS	• • • •	NodeJS	• • • • •
MySQL	• • • •	AWS	• • • • •
MongoDB	• • • •	Spark	• • • • •
HTTP/2	• • • •	JavaScript	• • • • •
Angular	• • • •	React/Next.js/Redux	• • • •
Vue/Vuex/Nuxt.js	• • • •	TypeScript	• • • • •
Bootstrap/Tailwind CSS/Material UI	• • • •	Express	• • • •

Professional Experience

Full Stack Developer

05/2020 - 02/2023

Simform

Optimized application performance by identifying and refactoring inefficient code, resulting in a 15% increase in speed.

Implemented automated tests and test suites, reducing the number of bugs by 25% and improving overall code quality by 20%.

Led full stack development for a customer-facing web application, resulting in 20% faster loading times and an improved UX/UI.

Web and Mobile Developer

03/2016 - 04/2020

Exist Software Labs

This was a good opportunity to learn and practise basic multiple languages for me. I was responsible for key-coding tasks with HTML/CSS/SCSS/SASS, JavaScript, React, Node.js, SQL, PHP/Laravel

Key achievement: Took junior level to senior by focusing on practicing the JavaScript, TypeScript, React and Node.js